Privacy Policy
==============

Effective from the 8th of August 2018. Last updated on the 10th of July 2023.

At ImprovMX, we respect the privacy rights of our users and recognize the importance of protecting the personal information we collect about you. Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand what information we collect and how we use and share that information. This Privacy Policy applies to our Websites and Services.

As used in this Privacy Policy, “**ImprovMX**,” “**us**” and “**we**” refers to ImprovMX, Inc. and its affiliates, including without limitation the “ImproveMX SAS”, company . The “**Websites**” means ImprovMX’s websites (including without limitation [www.improvmx.com](https://www.improvmx.com/), cdn.improvmx.com and any successor URLS, mobile or localized versions and related domains and subdomains), and the “**Services**” means ImprovMX’s applications and services, in each case in whatever format they may be offered now or in the future. The Websites and Services are collectively referred to herein as the “**Service**.”

Information We Collect
----------------------

**Registration and Contact Information.** We collect information about you when you (a) register to use the Services and (b) otherwise provide contact information to us via email, mail, or through our Service. This information you provide may include your username, first and last name, email address.

**Payment Information.** When you purchase the Services, we will also collect transaction information, which may include your company name, company VAT (when applicable), credit card information, billing and mailing address. We describe [how Payment Information are collected and processed](https://improvmx.com/pages/privacy#privacy-payments) later in this document.

**Technical, Usage and Location Information.** We automatically collect information on how you interact with the Service, such as the IP address from which you access the Service, date and time, referrer website and campaigns informations (“utm” fields). We may also collect location information, including location information automatically provided by your computer or device. We use cookies and similar technologies to collect some of this information. For more information, please see ImprovMX’s [Cookie Policy.](https://improvmx.com/pages/privacy#cookie-policy)

**Third Party Platforms.** We may collect information when you interact with our service on third-party sites or platforms, such as analyticals sites. This may include information such as actions or the fact that you viewed or interacted with our content.

**Other Information.**We may collect other information from you that is not specifically listed here. We may use any such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy or as otherwise permitted by you.

How We Use the Information We Collect
-------------------------------------

We use your information in the following ways:

* To provide, maintain and improve the Service and our other products and services, including to operate certain features and functionality of the Service (for example, by remembering your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during this or subsequent visits);
* To process your inquiries and otherwise deliver customer service;
* To process your payments, we share and use Payment Information as described in Section 4 (Payment Information);
* To control unauthorized use or abuse of the Service and our other products and services, or otherwise detect, investigate or prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal;
* To analyze trends, administer or optimize the Service, monitor usage or traffic patterns (including to track users’ movements around the Service) and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole;
* To communicate directly with you, including by sending you newsletters, promotions and special offers or information about new products and services. Your opt-out options for promotional communications are described in Section 6 (Your Controls and Choices);
* In the manner described to you at the time of collection or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

Sharing Your Information with Third Parties
-------------------------------------------

We do not sell, trade, share or transfer your personal information to third parties except in the following limited circumstances:

* We may share your personal information with our parent companies, subsidiaries and affiliates;
* We may share your personal information with third-party service providers to permit such parties to provide services that help us with our business activities, which may include assisting us with marketing, advertising our product/service offerings, or providing, maintaining and improving the features and functionality of the Service, among other things. For example, we may provide personal information to our service providers for direct emailing of our newsletters or notifications of our product/service offerings;
* We may share your personal information when we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce a Customer Agreement, including investigation of potential violations thereof, or (c) protect against imminent harm to our rights, property or safety, or that of our users or the public as required or permitted by law;
* We may share your personal information with third parties (including our service providers and government entities) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security or technical issues;
* We may share your personal information with our business partners who offer a service to you jointly with us, for example when running a cross-promotion;
* We may share your Payment Information to process your payments, as further described in Section 4 (Payment Information);
* We may share and/or transfer your personal information if we become involved in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or any form of sale of some or all of our assets; and
* We may share your personal information with a third party if we have your consent to do so.

We may also share aggregated or anonymized information with third parties for other purposes. Such information does not identify you individually, but may include usage, viewing and technical information such as the types of Service our customers and users generally use, the configuration of their computers, and performance metrics related to the use of Service which we collected through our technology. If we are required under applicable law to treat such information as personal information, then we will only disclose it as described above. Otherwise we may disclose such information for any reason.

Payment Information
-------------------

When you make a purchase on the Service, any credit card information you provide as part of your Payment Information is collected and processed directly by our payment processor Stripe through their Stripe Checkout service. We never receive or store your full credit card information. Stripe commits to complying with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS) and using industry standard security. Stripe may use your Payment Information in accordance with their own Privacy Policy here:[https://stripe.com/us/checkout/legal](https://stripe.com/us/checkout/legal).

Cookies
-------

### What are cookies?

Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website, mobile app or use an online platform. Cookies are widely used by online service providers to facilitate and help to make the interaction between users and websites, mobile apps and online platforms faster and easier, as well as to provide reporting information.

Cookies set by the website and/or mobile app and/or platform owner (in this case, ImprovMX) are called “first party cookies”. Cookies set by parties other than the website and/or mobile app and/or platform owner are called “third party cookies”.

Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website and/or mobile app and/or platform (e.g. like advertising, interactive content and analytics). The parties that set these third party cookies can recognise your computer or device both when it visits the website and/or mobile app and/or platform in question and also when it visits certain other websites and/or mobile apps and/or platforms.

### Why do we use cookies?

We use first party and third party cookies for several reasons. Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Websites and/or App and/or platform to operate, and we refer to these as “essential” or “strictly necessary” cookies. Other cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Websites and/or App and/or platform. Third parties serve cookies through our Websites and/or App and/or platform for analytics and other purposes. This is described in more detail below.

Services used
-------------

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **NAME** | **PURPOSE** |
| [AWS](https://crisp.chat/) | We use Amazon Web Services to host our infrastructure and handle email forwarding and custom sending via SMTP. |
| [OVHcloud](https://www.ovhcloud.com/) | We use OVHcloud to handle email forwarding and custom sending via SMTP. |
| [Intercom](https://intercom.com/) | Intercom is used on ImprovMX’s application to handle support on both Chat and Email. |
| [Fernand](https://getfernand.com/) | We use Fernand, the fastest and calmest customer support solution for SaaS, to provide exceptional support and enhance our customers’ experience. |
| [Customer.io](https://customer.io/) | We use Customer.io to send you emails related to your account and general messages like newsletters. |
| [Mailgun](https://www.mailgun.com/) | We use Mailgun to facilitate the sending of receipts and transactional emails. |
| Fetchlab | Fetchlab is a tool built by one of our Founder to display the logo of the domains you have on your dashboard and perform email validation when creating accounts. |
| [Amplitude](https://amplitude.com/) | We track a few key metrics on our service and Amplitude help us visualize them. All the data are anonymized. |
| [Linear](https://linear.app/) | We use Linear for internal issue tracking, project management and roadmap planning. |
| [Mixpanel](https://mixpanel.com/) | We use Mixpanel to gain valuable insights into user interactions with our product, enhancing user experience and engagement while respecting privacy. |
| [Plausible](https://plausible.io/) | We use Plausible, a privacy-friendly website analytics tool that does not use cookies, to gather insights into our website usage. |
| [ProfitWell](https://www.profitwell.com/) | We use ProfitWell Metrics for revenue reporting and financial analytics. |
| [Sentry](https://sentry.io/) | We use Sentry to retrieve, review and handle issues that might occurs within ImprovMX. |
| [Stripe](https://stripe.com/) | Our payment gateway. This allows us to accept credit card payments securely. |
| [Slack](https://slack.com/) | We use Stripe for team communications and automation of internal workflows. |
| [Trustpilot](https://www.trustpilot.com/) | We use Trustpilot’s Automatic Feedback Service to invite customers to share their experience about our products and services. |

### Cookies used

| VENDOR | COOKIE NAME | PURPOSE |
| --- | --- | --- |
| ImprovMX | \_t | Session tracking cookie. |
| Stripe | \_\_lc.visitor\_id.XXXXXXX, \_\_stripe\_mid, \_\_stripe\_orig\_props, stripe.csrf, cid, lang, machine\_identifier, merchant, mp\_{token}\_mixpanel, private\_machine\_identifier, lc\_window\_state | We rely on Stripe to handle payments made on ImprovMX. |

### How can I control cookies?

You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies. You can exercise your cookie preferences by clicking on the appropriate opt-out links provided in the cookie table above.

You can set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our Websites and/or App and/or platform though your access to some functionality and areas may be restricted. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser’s help menu for more information.

In addition, most advertising networks offer you a way to opt out of targeted advertising. If you would like to find out more information, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or[http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

### Blocking Cookies.

You can remove or block certain cookies using the settings in your browser but the Service may cease to function properly if you do so.

### Do Not Track Signals.

Your Web browser may have a “do not track” setting which, when enabled, causes your browser to send a do not track HTTP header file or “signal” to each site you visit. At present, the Service do not respond to this type of signal.

Sub-processors
--------------

We use the following 3rd party services to improve, understand troubleshoot, report bugs and provide support for you:

* **Google Analytics**  
    We use this service to understand general usage, traffic sources and to measure campaign success.
* **Hotjar**  
    We (also) use this service to understand general usage, traffic sources and to measure campaign success.
* **Amplitude**  
    We (also) use this service to understand general usage, traffic sources and to measure campaign success.
* **Stripe**  
    We use this service to handle all the payments made on the Service. The sole purpose is to increase security regarding the handle of sensible payments informations such as your credit cards details.
* **Mailgun**  
    We use this service to send emails on our behalf. The sole purpose is to increase email deliverability and success over sending via our own servers which may be blacklisted.

**REMEMBER**: We use these services only to provide you with a fantastic product that gives you easy access to things you like and to improve our general look and feel. If you choose to block, global opt out from some of the services that we use to deliver our product, you may run into errors, product bugs and other failures that influence your general experience and quality of our service. We are ok with that and respect your choice.

Other Access to or Disclosure of Your Information
-------------------------------------------------

The Service may also contain links to third party websites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us. Even if the third party is affiliated with us through a business partnership or otherwise, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third party. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy policies of such third parties to determine how they handle any information they separately collect from you. Please be aware that we do not warn you when you choose to click through to another website when using the Service.

The Websites contain features that enable you to post reviews, comments or other content that is publicly viewable. You should be aware that any personal information you submit as part of those posts can be read, collected, or used by other visitors to the Websites, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to publicly post on the Websites. Please see our [Website Terms of Use](https://improvmx.com/pages/privacy#)for more information and for other guidelines about posting content on the Websites.

Your Controls and Choices
-------------------------

Your data protection rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* If you wish to **access, correct, update, or request deletion** of your personal information, you can do so at any time by emailing [support@improvmx.com](mailto:support@improvmx.com).
* In addition, you can **object to the processing** of your personal information, ask us to **restrict the processing** of your personal information, or **request portability** of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by emailing [support@improvmx.com](mailto:support@improvmx.com).
* You have the right to **opt-out of marketing communications** we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing emails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing, please contact us by emailing [support@improvmx.com](mailto:support@improvmx.com).
* Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can **withdraw your consent** at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information
------------------------------------------------

When you use the Service, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information upon your request and either provide you the means to correct this information if it is inaccurate or to delete such information at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. You may access, review, correct, update, change or delete your information at any time. To do so, please contact us at [support@improvmx.com](mailto:support@improvmx.com) with your name and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed, or if you are using the Service, sign in to your account, go to your profile, and make the desired changes. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), jeopardize the privacy of others, would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

We may retain your information as necessary to support the Service, comply with our legal obligations or resolve disputes.

Changes to the Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate on this page the policy’s new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email or through notice on the Service.

No Children Under Age 13
------------------------

The Service are not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13, nor does ImprovMX knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, you may not attempt to register for the Service or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we confirm that we have collected personal information from someone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information promptly. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 and believe that we might have any information from or about such child, please contact us at the email or mailing address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

Your California Privacy Rights and Disclosures
----------------------------------------------

**California Shine the Light Law.** If you are a California resident and we disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes, California’s Shine the Light Law (CA Civil Code Section 1798.83) allows you to request certain information from us about such disclosures. To make a request under the Shine the Light Law, please contact us at [support@improvmx.com](mailto:support@improvmx.com). Please note that under California law, businesses are not required to respond to such requests more than once during any calendar year.

**California Information-Sharing Disclosure.** California residents may request a list of all third parties with respect to which we have disclosed any information about you for direct marketing purposes and the categories of information disclosed. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please send us a written request by email to [support@improvmx.com](mailto:support@improvmx.com) with “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line.

**California Minors.** At any time, you can delete or remove your posts using the same deletion or removal procedures described in Section [Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information](https://improvmx.com/pages/privacy#privacy-access-and-update) above, or otherwise through the Service. If you have questions about how to remove your posts or if you would like additional assistance with deletion you can contact our support team at [support@improvmx.com](mailto:support@improvmx.com).

Security
--------

The security of your personal information is important to us. We maintain a variety of appropriate technical and organizational safeguards to protect your personal information. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Further, we have implemented reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect personal information about you. When you enter sensitive information (such as your password), we encrypt that information in transit using industry-standard Transport Layer Security (TLS) encryption technology. No method of transmission over the Internet, method of electronic storage or other security methods are one hundred percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Contact Us
----------

If you have questions or need to contact us about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [support@improvmx.com](mailto:support@improvmx.com).
